Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
George B. Post architectural records
circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980)
New-York Historical Society
Post, George Browne, 1837-1913.
George B. Post & Sons
PR 53
approximately 1,014 Linear feet in 356 boxes of various size and 21 flat file drawers.
Records of the architectural firms of George B. Post and George B. Post & Sons. Among their best-known commissions are the Long Island Historical Society (1878–1879) [now Center for Brooklyn History], New York Stock Exchange (1901–1904) and the Wisconsin State Capitol (1904–1907). The collection consists of circa 8,600 architectural drawings, ink on linen and blueprints; circa 200 watercolor renderings, ink drawings, and pencil sketches; 75 packages of specifications; 5 albums of photographs; 1,000 separate photographs; 2 clipping scrapbooks (1882-1903); 5 letterpress books (1867-1884); circa 1,700 incoming letters (1872-1875); 1 ledger and 1 journal of Gambrill & Post (1864-1867); circa 60 financial ledgers and journals (1868-1951); 2 volumes of personnel employment records (1881-1918); 1 package of publications by firm members.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers by appointment only. To schedule an appointment, contact the Print Room Librarian at printroom@nyhistory.org. Portions of the collection are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Keep in mind that it will take between two (2) and five (5) business days for collections to arrive, and you should plan your research accordingly. The drawings in Subseries VI.F require one month to flatten and conserve before use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The bulk of the collection (Series I through V) was the gift of Edward E. Post, grandson of George B. Post, in 1956, with additions in 1972 and 1978. Series VI was the gift of Peter Post through Virginia Collyer, January 2003.
Arrangement
The collection is generally unprocessed, but is arranged in the following series:
Series I.
Rolled Drawings
Series II.
Flat Files
Series III.
Bound Volumes
Series IV.
Specifications
Series V.
Photographs and other material
Series VI.
2002 Accrual
Material is filed by format. Working drawings are in numbered sets according to project name; most renderings, competition entries, and sketches are alphabetical by project name; financial volumes are grouped by type (ledger, journal, cash book, staff pay record) and date; individual photographs are grouped by project name. Separate card indexes (in Subseries VI.A, Box 1, Enclosures 1-A and 1-B) provide access by project name for drawings and for photographs in two of the albums.
Perhaps the best guide to navigating the collection is Lisa B. Mausolf's 1983 Columbia University Masters Thesis, A Catalog of the Work of George B. Post, Architect (call no. PRINT ROOM NA737 .P63M3), which provides an alphabetical listing and chronological index to all of Post's known projects and indicates for which buildings the Society has study, presentation, and working drawings.
Biographical / Historical
George B(rowne) Post (b. New York City, 1837; d. Bernardsville, N.J., 1913) graduated from New York University in 1858 with a degree in civil engineering and worked as a draftsman for Richard Morris Hunt before opening an architectural office in New York in 1860 with Charles D. Gambrill. By 1868 Post had his own firm, and was engaged as the consulting architect in charge of elevators and ironwork for the Equitable Building (1868–70, demolished), considered the first skyscraper in New York City. He later designed the Western Union Building (1872–75, demolished) and used metal-framed interior walls in his New York Produce Exchange (1881–84, demolished) that anticipated the skeleton framing later adopted for skyscraper construction. Post is also known for such works as the Williamsburgh Savings Bank in Brooklyn (1868–75), the World (Pulitzer) Building (1889–90, demolished), the New York Stock Exchange (1901–4), and the campus of City College (1897–1907). His structural design skills and efficient, economical plans won him many honors, but only a handful of the more than 400 projects he undertook in New York City, Cleveland, Buffalo, and elsewhere have survived the urban rebuilding of the later twentieth century. Post is noted today for his tall arcaded buildings, which are among the first skyscrapers, and for his role in developing the modern office building. He also collaborated on lavish mansions for such clients as Cornelius Vanderbilt and Collis P. Huntington.
[This sketch combines details from Helena Zinkham, A Guide to Print, Photograph, Architecture & Ephemera Collections at The New-York Historical Society (New York: the Society, 1998), 124–25, and Sarah Bradford Landau, "George B(rowne) Post," in The Encyclopedia of New York City, 2nd edition (New Haven: Yale University Press, 2010), 1026–27. For more on Post, see Landau's George B. Post, Architect: Picturesque Designer and Determined Realist (New York: Monacelli Press, 1998); Winston Weisman, "George Browne Post," in Macmillan Encyclopedia of Architects (New York: The Free Press, 1982), vol. 3, 460–63; and, especially, Lisa B. Mausolf, A Catalog of the Work of George B. Post, Architect (Columbia University Master's Thesis, 1983).]
Major works of George B. Post
1868–1870 Equitable Life Assurance Company Building, New York
1872 Troy Savings Bank, N.Y.
1873–1875 Western Union Building
1874–1875 Chickering Hall, New York
1875 Williamsburgh Savings Bank, Brooklyn, N.Y.
1875–1876 New York Hospital
1878–1879 Long Island Historical Society Building [later Brooklyn Historical Society; now Center for Brooklyn History], Brooklyn, N.Y.
1879–1880 Smith Building
1880–1881 Post Building
1881–1883 Mills Building
1881–1885 Produce Exchange
1882–1893 Cornelius Vanderbilt House
1883–1885 Cotton Exchange
1884 Mortimer Building, New York
1884–1885 Hamilton Club, Brooklyn, N.Y.
1888–1890 New York Times Building (now part of Pace College)
1889–1890 Pulitzer Building Union Trust Company Building, New York
1890 Prudential Life Insurance Company Building, Newark, N.J.
1890–1893 Erie County Savings Bank, Buffalo, N.Y.
1890–1894 C. P. Huntington House
1891–1892 Havemeyer Building, New York
1893 Manufacturers and Liberal Arts Building, Chicago Exposition
1894 Bank of Pittsburgh
1895–1898 Weld Building, New York
1896 Park Building, Pittsburgh 636–638 Broadway, New York
1897–1899 Saint Paul Building
1897–1908 The College of the City of New York
1898–1899 Vincent Building
1901–1904 New York Stock Exchange, New York
1904–1907 Wisconsin State Capitol, Madison
1907–1908 Cleveland Trust Company, Ohio
1901–1911 334 Fourth Avenue, New York
1911–1912 Hotel Pontiac, Detroit Statler Hotel
1912 Williamson Building, Cleveland, Ohio
Chronology of George Browne Post, Architect, New York City (1865-1904), and Geo. B. Post & Sons, Architects, New York City (1904-1972) and Huntington, New York (1972-1990s)
1860–1904 George Browne Post commenced his practice in New York City, with C. D. Gambrill as his partner. He practiced by himself from 1865 to 1904.
1904–1913 George Brown Post and his sons, William S. Post and James Otis Post, Partners
1913–1920 William S. Post and James Otis Post, Partners
1920–1929 William S. Post, James Otis Post, and W. Sydney Wagner, Partners
1930–1937 James Otis Post
1937–1939 James Otis Post, Knut W. Lind, Partners. Edward Everett Post, employee until military service, 1940
1939–1944 James Otis Post
1944–1949 James Otis Post, Lessing Witford Williams, Partners
1946 Edward Everett Post after Navy discharge joins firm
1949–1951 James Otis Post, Edward Everett Post, and Lessing Whitford Williams, Partners
1951–1967 Edward Everett Post, Lessing Whitford Williams, Partners
1966 Ralph C. Colyer joined firm; opened branch office in Huntington, New York
1967–1975 Edward Everett Post, Ralph C. Colyer, Partners
1972 Entire office moved from New York City to Huntington, Long Island (N.Y.)
1975–1985 Edward Everett Post, President. Ralph C. Colyer, Vice President until his death
1986–1988 Edward Everett Post, sole officer
1988–1990 Edward Everett Post, President, Douglas P. Mattoon, Vice President
1990– Edward Everett Post, sole officer
Scope and Contents
The Society's collection contains most of the surviving records of Gambrill & Post (1860–1867), Geo. B. Post (1868–1905), and Geo. B. Post & Sons (founded 1905). Projects before 1890—for example, the Equitable Life Assurance and Western Union buildings in New York City—are covered primarily through financial journals, correspondence, photographs, and some 50 sketches and watercolor renderings by Post and by Edward A. Sargeant. For later projects, more documentation is usually available, from competition entries and developmental studies to working drawings, construction progress photographs, specifications, business ledgers, and publicity clippings. Sets of drawings document some 30 large hotels; 20 office buildings, including the St. Paul Building, New York; 20 banks and exchanges, including the New York Produce Exchange and the New York Stock Exchange; 10 apartment buildings and housing developments; 5 schools and colleges, including the College of the City of New York; the Wisconsin State Capitol; and more than 50 residences, many designed by William S. Post for relatives and neighbors in Bernardsville, New Jersey. Late commissions include an omnibus garage and the Netherlands Pavilion at the 1939–1940 New York World's Fair.
Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records.; Blueprints (reprographic copies); Clippings (information artifacts); Journals (accounts); Ledgers (account books); Letterpress copybooks.; Letters (correspondence); Personnel records.; Photographs.; Photograph albums.; Renderings (drawings); Scrapbooks.; Sketches.; Specifications.; Technical drawings.; Watercolors (paintings); Apartment houses.; Architecture, American -- 19th century -- Designs and plans.; Architecture, American -- 20th century -- Designs and plans.; Architecture, Domestic -- United States.; Bank buildings.; College buildings.; Commercial buildings -- United States -- Designs and plans.; Dwellings -- New Jersey.; Dwellings -- New York (State).; Dwellings -- Rhode Island -- Newport.; Historic buildings -- United States -- Designs and plans.; Hotels -- Designs and plans.; Office buildings -- Designs and plans.; Public buildings -- United States -- Design and plans.; Gambrill, Charles D. (Charles Dexter), 1832-1880; Huntington, Collis Potter, 1821-1900 -- Homes and haunts.; Post, William S.; Sargeant, Edward A.; Vanderbilt, Cornelius, 1843-1899 -- Homes and haunts.; Gambrill & Post (Firm); George B. Post & Sons; Belgian Pavilion (New York World's Fair, 1939-1940, New York, N.Y.); College of the City of New York (1866-1926) -- Buildings.; Equitable Life Assurance Building (New York, N.Y.); New York Produce Exchange -- Buildings.; New York Stock Exchange -- Buildings.; Western Union Building (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I. Rolled Drawings, 582 Linear feet in 142 boxes.
  Arrangement
  Filed geographically by state, then city, then by project title or client's name. The few Canadian projects follow the American, and uncertain locations are filed after Canada.
  The following drawings are unaccounted for (as of September 2021). Some might possibly be found among the rolled drawings of Subseries VI.F.
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 004 | Missouri—Kansas City | Clarke Estate | Medical Arts Building | preliminary plans
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 123 | Virginia—Warrington | Doeller | Residence
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 130 | Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 148 | Ohio—Cleveland | Chamber of Commerce
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 249 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 251 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 261 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Baskerville)
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 284? 289? | New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Mr. | Farm cottage
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 338 | New York—NYC—Bronx | Woodlawn Cemetery (between Walnut & Park Avenue)
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 343 | New Jersey—Bernardsville | Mitchell, C. B. | Brook Cottage additions
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 348 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Large scale architectural & blueprints
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 349 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Large scale architectural & blueprints
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 375 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 376 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Furniture)
  • Box: RD-###, Tube: 383 | New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building
  - California
    - California—Los Angeles | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-040, Tube 134)
    - California—Los Angeles | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-059, Tube 199)
  - Connecticut
    - Connecticut—Greenwich | Old Congregational Church | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 114)
    - Connecticut—Hartford | Hartford Hotel (Offsite-box RD-074, Tube 247)
    - Connecticut—Hartford | Proposed Hotel (Offsite-box RD-028, Tube 087-B)
    - Connecticut—Hartford | Proposed Hotel (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 119)
    - Connecticut—New Haven | Proposed Hotel (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 060)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Original tracings (Offsite-box RD-003, Tube 008)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | All scale details (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 010)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Private & Female wards (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 012-014)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Proposed change (Main Building) (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 012-014)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Record set of drawings (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 015)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Prints (Offsite-box RD-005, Tube 016)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | General cloth prints (Offsite-box RD-005, Tube 018-A)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | General cloth prints (Offsite-box RD-006, Tube 018-B)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Electrical & heating (original tracings) (Offsite-box RD-007, Tube 020)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Plans, elevations (Offsite-box RD-007, Tube 024)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Plot plans (survey) (Offsite-box RD-008, Tube 026)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Nurses home (Offsite-box RD-052, Tube 174-B)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 235)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital (Offsite-box RD-077, Tube 258)
    - Connecticut—Stamford | Stamford Hospital | Additions—Female & Private wards (Offsite-box RD-130, Tube 274)
    - Connecticut—Willimantic | Nathan Hale Hotel (Offsite-box RD-039, Tube 131)
  - Florida
    - Florida—Blake | N.T.A.C. Club Florida Chapter | Proposed plans (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 113)
    - Florida—Daytona | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-051, Tube 173-A)
    - Florida—Miami | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 084)
    - Florida—Miami | Reed, Harrison | Bungalow & garage (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 239)
    - Florida—Miami | Reed, Harrison | Residence (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 244)
    - Florida—Nichols | Locker Building (Offsite-box RD-064, Tube 217)
  - Indiana
    - Indiana—Indianapolis | Indianapolis Hotel garage (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 083)
  - Maine
    - Maine—Kittery | Portsmouth Navy Yard Development (Offsite-box RD-011, Tube 035-A)
    - Maine—Kittery | Portsmouth Navy Yard Development (Offsite-box RD-011, Tube 035-B)
    - Maine—Kittery | Portsmouth Navy Yard Development (Offsite-box RD-011, Tube 035-C)
    - Maine—Kittery | Portsmouth Navy Yard Development (Offsite-box RD-011, Tube 035-D)
  - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts—Boston | Manger Hotel (Offsite-box RD-103, Tube 330-A)
    - Massachusetts—Boston | Manger Hotel (Offsite-box RD-103, Tube 330-B)
    - Massachusetts—Framingham | Monroe, Dr. | Cottage (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 120)
  - Missouri
    - Missouri—Kansas City | Clarke Estate | Medical Arts Building | preliminary plans (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 004)
    - Missouri—Kansas City | Clarke Estate | Medical Arts Building | blueprints (Offsite-box RD-113, Tube 359)
    - Missouri—Kansas City | Clarke Estate | Medical Arts Building | cloth drawings & details (Offsite-box RD-131, Tube 360)
  - Nebraska
    - Nebraska—Omaha | City plans (Offsite-box RD-058, Tube 196)
  - New Jersey
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 041)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 102)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 104)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 109)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 120)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 220)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Hotel (Offsite-box RD-047, Tube 160)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Child's Restaurant (Offsite-box RD-031, Tube 098)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 061-A)
    - New Jersey—Atlantic City | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 150)
    - New Jersey—Basking Ridge | Basking Ridge Presbyterian Church (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 236)
    - New Jersey—Basking Ridge | Basking Ridge School | Alterations & Additions (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 104)
    - New Jersey—Basking Ridge | Presbyterian Cemetery | Childs Monument (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 103)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Anderson | Farm house (Offsite-box RD-039, Tube 129)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Bernardsville Library | Stock room (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 149)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Bradley, William H. | Alterations to Hill Farm Cottage (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 281-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Bradley, William H. | Alterations to Hill Farm Cottage (Offsite-box RD-084, Tube 281-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Campbell, Mrs. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 107)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Condick, Ms. [Mrs. Condict?] | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-075, Tube 252)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Condict, Mrs. [Ms. Condick?] | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 229)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Dryden, John F. | Cottage (Offsite-box RD-052, Tube 177)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Dryden, John F. | Residence | Additions for Thatcher M. Adams (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 115)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Engelhard, Charles | Gardener's Cottage (Offsite-box RD-047, Tube 162)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Fisk, Haley | Residence | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 119)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | La Roque, Joseph: Farm house, Alteration; & La Roque, Joseph Jr.: Proposed residence (Offsite-box RD-036, Tube 118-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Le Roy Residence (Offsite-box RD-128, Tube ###)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lewis, E. A. | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-052, Tube 175)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lewis, G. A. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-036, Tube 117)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lindabury, R. | Gardener's cottage (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 151)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lindabury, R. | Residence alterations & additions (Offsite-box RD-046, Tube 158)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lloyd, F. | Dining room alterations (Offsite-box RD-053, Tube 179)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Lloyd, F. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-040, Tube 133)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Italian Chapel Parsonage (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 146)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Methodist Episcopal Parsonage (Offsite-box RD-039, Tube 127)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Mitchell, Clarence B. | Bedell House (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 115)
      Other Finding Aids
      This project is more fully described in a previous, partial finding aid.
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Mitchell, C. B. | Brook Cottage additions (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 343)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Moran, Charles A. | Farm house & stable (Offsite-box RD-086, Tube 291-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Moran, Charles A. | Farm house & stable (Offsite-box RD-087, Tube 291-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Moran, Charles A. | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-046, Tube 157)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Nurses home (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 122-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Nurses home (Offsite-box RD-038, Tube 122-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Peters, T. M. | Claremont House (formerly G. B. Post residence) (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 279)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Peters, T. M. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-024, Tube 075)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Peters, T. M. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 279)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Claremont (house) (Offsite-box RD-079, Tube 266-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Claremont (house) (Offsite-box RD-080, Tube 266-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Claremont (house) (Offsite-box RD-079, Tube 266-Annex)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Dwelling, Claremont Road (Offsite-box RD-025, Tube 078)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Residence & alterations (Offsite-box RD-028, Tube 088-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Residence & alterations (Offsite-box RD-028, Tube 088-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Residence—"House for Mrs. George Post Jr., designed by W. S. Post" (Offsite-box RD-108, Tube 344-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, George B. | Residence—"House for Mrs. George Post Jr., designed by W. S. Post" (Offsite-box RD-108, Tube 344-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, Mrs. George B. | Farm house (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 106)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, Mrs. George B. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-059, Tube 200-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, Mrs. George B. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-059, Tube 200-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, Mrs. George B. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-059, Tube 200-C)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, Mrs. George B. | Stable & chicken house (Offsite-box RD-024, Tube 072)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Post, William G. [actually William "S"] | Stable (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 081)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Pyne, Percy R., Esq. | Coachman's cottage (Offsite-box RD-129, Tube 043)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Pyne, Mrs. Percy | Alterations & additions to cottage (Offsite-box RD-008, Tube 025)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Roebling, John A. | Residence | Servant's wing (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 071)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Squibb, Charles | Additions to house (Offsite-box RD-130, Tube 289?)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Squibb, Charles | Additions to house (Offsite-box RD-133, Tube 289?)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Squibb, Charles | Residence alterations & additions (Offsite-box RD-051, Tube 173-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Stevens, R. J. | Residence | Additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 044)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Turnbull, Mrs. | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 228-A)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Turnbull, Mrs. | House & stable (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 228-B)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Virginia Day Nursery (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 218)
    - New Jersey—Bernardsville | Whitenack Cottage | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 108)
    - [New Jersey—Bernardsville?] | Palmer Campbell | Stable additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 085)
    - New Jersey—Englewood | Citizen's National Bank (Offsite-box RD-030, Tube 096)